Get everyone from Tan Zuoyan's department together right now.
اجمعوا جميع العاملين في قسم تان زويان الآن.
Call an emergency meeting for the Autumn Winter Alpine Collection.
عقد اجتماع طارئ لمجموعة الخريف والشتاء الألبية.
You!
أنت!
So, are you going
إذن، هل ستذهب؟
or not?
أم لا؟
Just so you know,
للعلم فقط،
there are plenty of people eyeing this project.
هناك الكثير من الأشخاص الذين يتطلعون إلى هذا المشروع.
Alright, Zuoyan.
حسناً يا زويان.
Just focus on your work for now.
ركز على عملك في الوقت الحالي.
Work comes first.
العمل يأتي أولاً.
I'll do whatever you say.
سأفعل كل ما تقوله.
Where did he touch you?
أين لمسك؟
Here?
هنا؟
Or here?
أو هنا؟
Li Shujing. What exactly are you trying to do?
لي شوجينغ. ما الذي تحاول فعله بالضبط؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I'm Zuoyan's fiancée.
أنا خطيبة زويان.
Isn't the wedding
أليس الزفاف
something we have to prepare for sooner or later?
شيء يجب أن نستعد له عاجلاً أم آجلاً؟
I know exactly what is really going on between you two.
أعرف تماماً ما يحدث بينكما.
Does telling this lie even mean anything?
هل لهذه الكذبة أي معنى؟
This could be a lie,
قد يكون هذا كذباً.
or it could be the truth.
أو ربما تكون هذه هي الحقيقة.
Why not
ولم لا
give me everything I want?
أعطني كل ما أريد؟
Can you do that?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
If you can,
إن أمكنك ذلك،
I promise,
أعدك،
at the wedding,
في حفل الزفاف،
I'll wear only the shackles you gave me.
لن أرتدي إلا الأغلال التي أعطيتني إياها.
Didn't you
ألم تفعل ذلك؟
want to put these shackles on me eight years ago?
هل تريد أن تضع هذه الأغلال عليّ قبل ثماني سنوات؟
Now you're the one wearing them,
الآن أنت من يرتديها،
while watching me walk the red carpet
أثناء مشاهدتي وأنا أسير على السجادة الحمراء
over the Tan Group's ruin.
على خلفية انهيار مجموعة تان.
You want to play with fire?
هل تريد أن تلعب بالنار؟
I can burn the entire Tan Group
أستطيع أن أحرق مجموعة تان بأكملها
into your bridal chamber.
إلى غرفة زفافك.
But remember,
لكن تذكر،
the ones locked in these flames
أولئك المحاصرون في هذه النيران
will only be two dead people, you and me.
لن يكون هناك سوى شخصين ميتين، أنت وأنا.
=Secret By My Name=
=سر باسمي=
(Adapted from the novel Hotpot Loves Tangyuan by Ye Yijian)
(مقتبس من رواية "هوت بوت يعشق تانغ يوان" للكاتبة يي ييجيان)
=Episode 5= You little shorty,
=الحلقة 5= يا قصير القامة،
why are you picking a fight with me?
لماذا تفتعل مشكلة معي؟
You grew taller but not any smarter.
لقد ازداد طولك، لكنك لم تزد ذكاءً.
Playing deaf and mute with me every single day, are you?
هل تتظاهر بالصمم والبكم معي كل يوم؟
Who are you calling brainless?
من أنت أيها الأحمق؟
Li Shujing, are you out of your mind?
لي شوجينغ، هل فقدت عقلك؟
Who are you calling crazy?
من الذي تصفه بالمجنون؟
Lin Xi, listen.
لين شي، استمعي.
Stop playing innocent.
توقف عن التظاهر بالبراءة.
You only got where you are by being Tan Jianfei's living seal.
لم تصل إلى ما أنت عليه إلا لأنك كنت الفقمة الحية لتان جيانفي.
Do you really think you are the Group's lucky charm now?
هل تعتقد حقاً أنك تميمة حظ المجموعة الآن؟
Miss Li.
الآنسة لي.
How noble you must be.
كم أنت نبيل!
With trash drafts like this, you are worse than a third-rate designer,
بمسودات رديئة كهذه، أنت أسوأ من مصمم من الدرجة الثالثة.
and you're trying to apply for a top-level patent?
وأنت تحاول التقدم بطلب للحصول على براءة اختراع من المستوى الأعلى؟
Do you really think Tan Group belongs to your family?
هل تعتقد حقاً أن مجموعة تان تنتمي إلى عائلتك؟
I will ask one last time. Are you signing this or not?
سأسأل للمرة الأخيرة. هل ستوقع على هذا أم لا؟
I am not signing it. No!
لن أوقعها. لا!
Even if Tan Jianfei comes, I'm not signing.
حتى لو جاء تان جيانفي، فلن أوقع.
Sign it or do not, I do not care.
وقّعها أو لا، لا يهمني.
Li Shujing is a madwoman!
لي شوجينغ امرأة مجنونة!
Tan Jianfei.
تان جيانفي.
So this is the kind of crazy woman
هذا هو نوع المرأة المجنونة
you rejected my engagement for back then?
هل رفضت خطوبتي بسبب ذلك الوقت؟
Is it interesting?
هل هو أمر مثير للاهتمام؟
That crazy woman treats me like a live target.
تلك المرأة المجنونة تعاملني كهدف حي.
And you call this interesting?
وتسمي هذا مثيراً للاهتمام؟
Do you still want me to do this project for you?
هل ما زلت تريدني أن أقوم بهذا المشروع من أجلك؟
The project is yours.
المشروع ملكك.
But I am quite interested in watching this show.
لكنني مهتم جدًا بمشاهدة هذا البرنامج.
Let me remind you of one thing.
دعني أذكرك بشيء واحد.
Li Shujing
لي شوجينغ
is not someone to mess with.
ليس شخصاً يُستهان به.
Tan Jianfei.
تان جيانفي.
Are you using me to deal with Li Shujing,
هل تستخدمني للتعامل مع لي شوجينغ؟
or throwing me out there for her to shoot at?
أم أنها ترمي بي هناك لتطلق النار عليّ؟
What exactly is going on with this project?
ما الذي يحدث بالضبط في هذا المشروع؟
Hang in there.
اصبر.
Hang...
يشنق...
Hey!
يا!
Please move.
يرجى التحرك.
Tan Jianfei!
تان جيانفي!
Hang in there, my foot!
اصمد يا قدمي!
It makes me so mad!
هذا الأمر يثير غضبي بشدة!
That woman launched a charity collaboration and took away
أطلقت تلك المرأة مبادرة تعاون خيري واستحوذت على
seventy percent of our pre-sales.
سبعون بالمائة من مبيعاتنا المسبقة.
She monopolizes fabric suppliers under the banner of charity.
إنها تحتكر موردي الأقمشة تحت ستار العمل الخيري.
The whole industry is siding with her.
الصناعة بأكملها تقف إلى جانبها.
Even the board is pressuring me.
حتى مجلس الإدارة يضغط عليّ.
They force me to halt the Autumn Winter Alpine project.
يجبرونني على إيقاف مشروع جبال الألب الخريفية الشتوية.
Tan Jianfei went all out just to keep me away from this project.
بذل تان جيانفي كل ما في وسعه لإبعادي عن هذا المشروع.
This is infuriating.
هذا أمر مثير للغضب.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Her so-called ethical business
أعمالها التي تدعي أنها أخلاقية
is far from spotless.
إنها بعيدة كل البعد عن أن تكون نظيفة تماماً.
Look.
ينظر.
The rural factories she partners with
المصانع الريفية التي تتعاون معها
cannot meet production at all.
لا يمكن تلبية متطلبات الإنتاج على الإطلاق.
Those so-called handwoven textiles
تلك المنسوجات التي تسمى المنسوجات اليدوية
(Revealing the Fraud Behind the Rural Poverty-Relief Weaving Factory)
(كشف الاحتيال وراء مصنع النسيج الذي يهدف إلى تخفيف حدة الفقر في المناطق الريفية)
(and the Shell-Company Shareholding Structure)
(وهيكل ملكية أسهم الشركات الوهمية)
are actually mass-produced goods
هي في الواقع سلع منتجة بكميات كبيرة
repackaged from overseas factories.
مُعاد تغليفها من مصانع خارجية.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
(Xijie Apparel Legal Representative: Tan Jianfei 75%)
(الممثل القانوني لشركة Xijie Apparel: Tan Jianfei 75%)
This company's legal representative...
الممثل القانوني لهذه الشركة...
(Xijie Apparel Legal Representative: Tan Jianfei 75%)
(الممثل القانوني لشركة Xijie Apparel: Tan Jianfei 75%)
This is a shell company
هذه شركة وهمية
controlled by Tan Jianfei.
تحت سيطرة تان جيانفي.
Lin Xi is claiming the moral high ground to clean up Tan Group's image.
يدّعي لين شي أنه صاحب الموقف الأخلاقي الرفيع لتنظيف صورة مجموعة تان.
Send all this to the media immediately.
أرسل كل هذا إلى وسائل الإعلام فوراً.
There is more.
وهناك المزيد.
The so-called poverty relief workshop in her promo shut down two years ago.
أُغلقت ورشة العمل التي وصفتها بـ"ورشة الإغاثة من الفقر" في حملتها الترويجية قبل عامين.
We can find a few former workers and put them on camera.
يمكننا العثور على بعض العمال السابقين وتصويرهم.
We will tear apart her carefully crafted charity image.
سنمزق صورتها الخيرية المصطنعة بعناية.
Even so,
ومع ذلك،
we still cannot
ما زلنا غير قادرين
reclaim the Autumn Winter Alpine project.
استعادة مشروع جبال الألب الخريفية الشتوية.
And we may be facing
وقد نواجه
an even fiercer backlash from them.
بل ورد فعل عنيف منهم.
The top priority now
الأولوية القصوى الآن
is to find her weakness as soon as possible.
الهدف هو إيجاد نقطة ضعفها في أسرع وقت ممكن.
She drew this family portrait
رسمت هذه الصورة العائلية
when she was seven.
عندما كانت في السابعة من عمرها.
She didn't finish the old man's face.
لم تُكمل رسم وجه الرجل العجوز.
Do you think she already sensed
هل تعتقد أنها شعرت بذلك بالفعل؟
that Tan Group would one day
أن مجموعة تان ستفعل ذلك يوماً ما
drive her family to ruin?
هل ستؤدي إلى خراب عائلتها؟
You still love
ما زلت تحب
digging through old trash,
البحث في النفايات القديمة،
just like you did
تمامًا كما فعلت أنت
when you stole her diary back then.
عندما سرقت مذكراتها في ذلك الوقت.
You were the one who said
أنت من قال
Shujing would marry me one day,
ستتزوجني شوجينغ يوماً ما،
and I had to protect her.
وكان عليّ أن أحميها.
Now you say you want to marry her yourself.
والآن تقول إنك تريد الزواج منها بنفسك.
Zuoyan,
زويان،
your acting is terrible.
تمثيلك سيء للغاية.
A performance this clumsy
أداء بهذا القدر من الركاكة
will not last very long.
لن يدوم طويلاً.
Well,
حسنًا،
people change.
الناس يتغيرون.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
the old man was set on making me inherit Tan Group.
كان الرجل العجوز مصمماً على أن أرث مجموعة تان.
But what happened later?
لكن ماذا حدث لاحقاً؟
He changed.
لقد تغير.
Shujing changed too.
شوجينغ تغيرت أيضاً.
She will not love you anymore.
لن تحبك بعد الآن.
She will marry me,
ستتزوجني،
and the one who protects her will be me.
وسأكون أنا من يحميها.
The way you protect her
الطريقة التي تحميها بها
is by turning her into a sacrifice of the Tan family.
وذلك بتحويلها إلى قربان لعائلة تان.
Do you even know what you are doing?
هل تعرف حتى ما الذي تفعله؟
If she were to find out
لو أنها اكتشفت ذلك
that you do not carry Tan blood at all,
أنك لا تحمل دم تان على الإطلاق،
do you think she would stay with you?
هل تعتقد أنها ستبقى معك؟
Do you think she cares about that?
هل تعتقد أنها تهتم بذلك؟
She has known everything for a long time.
لقد كانت على علم بكل شيء منذ فترة طويلة.
And yet she still chose to marry me. Why?
ومع ذلك، اختارت الزواج بي. لماذا؟
Because only I can.
لأنني الوحيد القادر على ذلك.
Only me.
أنا فقط.
I am the only one who can give her what she wants most.
أنا الوحيد القادر على منحها ما تريده بشدة.
What you want most is nothing more than what little the Tan family has left.
أكثر ما تريده هو ما تبقى لدى عائلة تان من القليل.
What Shujing wants
ما يريده شوجينغ
is for the entire Tan family to be wiped out.
إن الهدف هو إبادة عائلة تان بأكملها .
-And me... -And you.
وأنا... وأنت.
The bloodline of the Tan family she hates most
سلالة عائلة تان التي تكرهها أكثر من غيرها
is flowing through your veins.
يجري في عروقك.
Jianfei,
جيانفي،
every time you touch her,
في كل مرة تلمسها،
what do you feel?
ما هو شعورك؟
Is it her warmth,
هل هو دفئها؟
or the rough feel of the rope your father used to strangle her father?
أم الملمس الخشن للحبل الذي استخدمه والدك لخنق والدها؟
Li Shujing, I can't stand you anymore.
لي شوجينغ، لم أعد أطيقك.
You asked me out and still showed up
لقد طلبت مني الخروج معك، ومع ذلك حضرت.
late...
متأخر...
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Where is Li Shujing?
أين هو لي شوجينغ؟
Mr. Tan,
السيد تان،
you don't look like you're here to talk business.
لا يبدو أنك هنا للتحدث عن العمل.
This drink is called Thorn Kiss.
يُطلق على هذا المشروب اسم "قبلة الشوك".
Tell me,
أخبرني،
does it taste anything like
هل طعمه يشبه أي شيء آخر؟
the Wild Lemon you forced into my mouth when we were eighteen?
الليمونة البرية التي أجبرتني على وضعها في فمي عندما كنا في الثامنة عشرة من عمرنا؟
So are you pretending to be drunk?
هل تتظاهر بأنك ثمل؟
Too bad you are this wasted,
يا للأسف أنك ثملٌ إلى هذه الدرجة!
you cannot even mix a proper drink.
لا يمكنك حتى تحضير مشروب مناسب.
You really should learn from your brother.
يجب عليك حقاً أن تتعلم من أخيك.
He could turn poison into champagne.
كان بإمكانه تحويل السم إلى شمبانيا.
♪I remember your smile again♪
أتذكر ابتسامتك مجدداً.
The way you call me Mr. Tan
الطريقة التي تناديني بها السيد تان
is unbearably fake.
مزيف بشكل لا يطاق.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
the words you said when you bit into my collarbone
الكلمات التي قلتها عندما عضضت عظمة الترقوة خاصتي
sounded far more honest.
بدا الأمر أكثر صدقاً بكثير.
Tan Jianfei,
تان جيانفي،
why do you always
لماذا تفعل ذلك دائماً
act like the victim?
هل يتصرفون كضحايا؟
It was your Tan family
كانت عائلة تان الخاصة بك
that dragged me into hell first.
هذا ما جرّني إلى الجحيم أولاً.
But why are you suddenly
لكن لماذا أنت فجأة
playing the savior?
هل تلعب دور المنقذ؟
♪Have you ever heard that?♪
هل سمعت بهذا من قبل؟
♪What we lose makes us grow♪
ما نفقده يجعلنا ننمو.
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
Do you know what I hate most about you?
هل تعلم ما أكرهه فيك أكثر من أي شيء آخر؟
I hate you for making me measure my hatred.
أكرهك لأنك أجبرتني على قياس كراهيتي.
Too much, and I fear I'll soften.
إذا بالغت في ذلك، أخشى أن ألين.
Too little, and I fear it'll show.
إذا كان قليلاً جداً، فأخشى أن يظهر ذلك.
♪Give me just one more moment♪
أعطني لحظة أخرى فقط!
♪Thinking of your face, I wish to repay what I owe you♪
أفكر في وجهك، وأتمنى أن أردّ لك ما أدين به.
♪Why is there no forever?♪
لماذا لا يوجد شيء اسمه الأبدية؟
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه.
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
هل نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي؟
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق؟
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
مع انقشاع الضباب، البحث عن علاج النور؟
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ.
♪An ending that can never be undone♪
نهاية لا يمكن التراجع عنها أبداً
♪Disrupting the old rhythm, laying traps♪
تعطيل الإيقاع القديم، ونصب الفخاخ؟
♪A board full of snares♪
لوحة مليئة بالفخاخ؟
♪Carving the past into every smile and word♪
???نقش الماضي في كل ابتسامة وكلمة؟
♪After falling, still searching for♪
بعد السقوط، ما زال يبحث عن؟
♪The old marks♪
العلامات القديمة
♪Pages filled with attempts to hide the past♪
صفحات مليئة بمحاولات إخفاء الماضي؟
♪The next page♪
الصفحة التالية
♪Is turned, revealing this land of right and wrong♪
انقلبت الأمور، كاشفةً عن هذه الأرض التي تنقسم إلى حق وباطل.
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه.
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
هل نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي؟
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق؟
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
مع انقشاع الضباب، البحث عن علاج النور؟
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ.
♪The way I came♪
الطريقة التي أتيت بها؟